♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hey, Meg. Where are you going?
Are you kidding? The Olympic
qualifiers are today.
- I'm competing.
- In what?
- I'm a bi...
- Knew it.
- Athlete.
- Didn't know it.
If I win today, I'm
going to the Olympics.
Why is this the first
we're hearing about this?
It's not. God, how could you
guys not know about this?
I've been training for years.
Peter. Peter, I need you
to hold my ears. Aah!
Oh. Oh.
Who wants chowder?
Okay, I'm off to go
train for the Olympics.
Ew!
Mom? Mommy? Mommy?
Mommy? Mama?
Hey, Ma, I'm gonna go
train for the Olympics.
Mama? Mama? Ma?
My goal becomes clear:
the broccoli must die.
All right, I'm off to
train for the Olympics.
See? I've been training
since I was Lacey Chabert.
- So, are you guys gonna come?
- I don't know.
The Yule Log Channel
just put on another log,
and I really like it when the
wood goes "crack, crack,
pop, crack, pop."
We all like that. Sorry, Meg.
That's okay.
I guess I'll just drive
there by myself...
in my Jeep!
Wait a minute. You have a Jeep?
Well, why didn't you say so?
Come on, family!
Let's go do TV commercial driving meant
for a professional driver
on a closed course.
Jeep: The toughest
four-letter word on wheels.
For the driver who doesn't
like to stop going
just because they've run out of road.
Ow, my balls! Why'd you do that?
Head out where the real fun begins.
There was plenty of road left!
Where the paved roads leave off.
Aah! My balls! It's too bumpy.
Potholes and bumps and ruts
can come as they will.
Ah, they're getting
rattled and smushed.
Jeep's welded, rugged
and riveted frame...
Please go back on the road!
Takes punishment in large doses...
- My balls!
- And comes back for more!
I like safe driving. My balls!
Thanks again for coming, guys.
It really means a lot to me.
Of course, honey. We wouldn't miss it.
Plus, it's a good excuse
to put on my winter coat
and find items from last
year still in the pocket.
Ooh, sticky pennies, a
rock-hard Starburst,
an appointment card for my
next dental appointment
that's already come and gone,
a ticket stub for a
matinee of Interstellar,
an unwrapped piece of Dentyne,
a yarmulke from when
that Jewish guy died,
a breath mint from the
now-defunct Clorets corporation,
printed-out Mapquest
directions to Dave & Buster's,
Iron Man Band-Aid,
Flintstone vitamin I didn't
take 'cause it was Barney,
refrigerator magnet
from local electrician
who is now arrested,
and balled up tissues with
last year's flu on it.
You done with your pocket bits?
It's freezing!
So the biathlon combines
cross-country skiing
- and rifle shooting?
- Yeah.
Well, that doesn't sound so hard.
Can I try?
I don't know if that's a good idea.
My event starts soon.
Meg, it is my duty as
a bad father to prove
that I can do anything my kids can do.
Okay, fine.
Here we go.
All right, I think I'm
getting the hang of it.
I have to say, I'm very proud of Meg.
Who knew she was good at something?
Yeah, does anybody else in the
family have any secret talents
we don't know about?
I'm the Quahog edging champion.
That's great, Chris. Now what's that?
It's the practice of
erotic sexual denial.
Go wait in the car.
And no edging!
But he did continue edging,
bringing himself to the
verge of sexual pleasure,
only to stop at the last moment.
I'm Ron Howard, and I do voice-overs
for this show now, too.
But that was the only voice-over
Ron Howard did for the show.
He asked for too much money.
I'm Kristen Bell, and I do
reasonably-priced voice-overs.
But her voice-overs
were not reasonably priced,
so they turned to me,
a guy who sounds like Morgan Freeman,
but is not, in fact, Morgan Freeman.
My name is Josh Robert Thompson,
and I perform for scale.
You're going down, Meg.
- Lacey Chabert?!
- That's right.
This should be my Olympics.
- Shut up, Meg.
- No, you shut up, Meg.
No, you shut up, Meg.
Shut up, Megs!
Yay, Meg!
Wow. Meg is going to the Olympics!
Let's celebrate by burning our lips
on vending machine hot chocolate.
- Ow!
- Ugh!
Mine has whipped cream,
so I didn't get it
on the first sip.
Ow!
_
Thank you.
Um, I-I'm not really
good at public speaking,
so I'll just say...
farble shlup muckle blop.
All right, Meg, I'll take it from here.
Hi. I'm Lois Griffin, Meg's mother.
You may also know me as the lady
who threw a plate of cheese
during that city council meeting.
But we got the streets
plowed, though, right?
The cheese worked, yeah.
I just wanted to say how proud
we are of Meg's accomplishment.
So it looks like the Griffins are going
to the Winter Olympics in Korea!
Do you think there'll be a gag
about the Jamaican bobsled team?
- No, probably not.
- Oh.
'Cause I was working on
my exaggerated shiver.
Burr. Burr. Oh.
Yeah, man, it be cold.
Okay, okay, yeah, yeah, maybe.
There might be. Don't-don't go far.
Don't go far.
My race isn't for a few days,
so we should have plenty
of time to hang out.
Anyone want to grab some food?
Sorry, Meg, I can't.
I'm trying to land you
some endorsements,
and I have a lead with a
very popular IBS medication.
Quick, say,
"I never let traveler's
diarrhea keep me grounded."
No!
Well, then you're just handing
this thing right to John Kruk!
_
Oh, my God, Brian, look.
- Who is that?
- Oh, that's figure skater
turned flamboyant
commentator Johnny Weir.
I wonder where Tara Lipinski is.
I heard they always have to be
within quipping distance of each other.
Oh, she's in the hat!
Isn't she amazing?
I feel like she's my soul mate.
How is she your soul mate?
She looks like a baby,
and she's best friends with a gay guy.
- Her life is my life.
- I'm not gay.
Well, it's not me!
Come on, let's go meet them.
Hi. I just had to come
over and introduce myself.
My name is Stewie, and I'm
a huge fan of you guys.
Oh, it's nice to meet you, Stewie.
Yeah, it's always so
nice to meet our fans.
And can I just say, the shape
of your head is stunning.
Really? I get a lot of grief for it.
Some people say it
looks like a football.
Okay, I don't know what that
is, but they're just jealous.
Every one of them.
Remember, nothing normal looks good.
Well, I have to say, you
two are the best thing
to happen to sports
since the New York Knicks
finally changed their name.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your 2018
New York Pieces-Of-Dog-.
Bitty bitty bop.
Funky, funky.
_
Wow, I can't believe
I'm on a first-name basis
with Tara Lipinski.
Now, refresh my memory: is
Tara the one who had the DUI?
No, that's Oksana Baiul!
Oh, sounds like something Gandalf says
at the foot of a mountain.
Oksana Baiul!
Okay, we can go in now.
Oh, God, here she comes!
Act like I said something funny.
I don't know, Stewie.
I think the Special Olympics
serve an important purpose.
So do I! Who thinks they don't?
I don't know. Ask this guy.
He's a dog. He's just
learning how to talk.
So, hey, Tara, are you
doing anything later?
I was thinking maybe we could
grab dinner or something.
Yeah, sure. You seem cool.
That could be fun.
All right then, it's a date.
Oh, I just need to make a call.
I was supposed to help
the speed skaters
get their tights over their thighs.
Stewie, it's not gonna fit!
Hey, we can do this.
I worked with Garth Brooks.
Shirt and pants.
Little secret... Garth wears leggings.
The denim pattern is projected on.
Hello, Kansas City!
Stick to the agreed-upon
choreography, please.
Ask who else has friends in low places.
Hey, who else here has
friends in low places?
All right, we got 'em back, baby.
Whoa, Ryan Lochte?
- Uh, where?
- You.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, are you athlete?
No, I just like wearing clothes
that feel like pajamas.
That's most of what being athlete is.
Wait, aren't you a summer sport guy?
Oh... it's cold.
Here's a beer. Follow me.
Peter partied all night
with international bozo Ryan Lochte.
And this voice-over
was actually covered
by my original payment.
Stewie, I'm very impressed.
I didn't know you skated.
Yeah, well, there's a lot
you don't know about me.
Like I'm always full of surprises.
- Did it work?
- Yes. Yeah.
You were supposed to be quiet!
Would you like to join me for a dance?
Wow!
But that's not how it really happened.
Would you like to join me for a dance?
Oh-ho! Wow.
Ow! Ow! I bit my tongue!
- I swallowed the piece!
- Oh, my God, are you okay?
Don't go on the ice. It's too slippery.
I'll crawl back. Don't watch me.
- Hi, hi, hi.
- Oh. Hey, Johnny.
I'm just gonna run to the
bathroom real quick. B-R-B.
Oh, she's a regular Tinkle Britches.
Get the hell out of here,
you little maggot.
Wha-Wha... Johnny?
- What happened to your voice?
- This is my voice.
You think I actually talk like that?
That's just something I do
to get the skater chicks.
- Does Tara know?
- Nah. She don't like guys like me.
She likes guys like me.
Wait, but she had a great
time with me tonight.
Yeah, that's what she does
with her gay friends.
But you're her gay friend.
What'd you say, you little?!
Is everything okay out here?
Yeah, I was just looking at his shirt.
I love this Nordstrom Rack.
How was the tinkle?
It was good. I also dumped.
You're so bad.
Anyway, sad emoji face,
Stewie has to leave.
Oh. Okay. Bye, Stewie.
I had a wonderful time.
Me... me, too.
Not as good as I'm gonna have.
And I know what a football is.
Killed me to say that.
Hey, you flush underwear
in train toilet?!
Yeah, they, uh, th-they were done.
This illegal. I want you off train!
What are you gonna do about it?
You're just a train conductor...
who has a huge kicking foot?
Aah! Oh!
Where the hell am I?
Oh, my God, I'm in the wrong Korea.
That's it. Like your missiles,
I'm about to go ballistic.
But that's not how it really happened.
That's it. Like your missiles,
I'm about to go ballistic.
Ow! A northern bird flew into my nuts!
Go to commercial.
That's weird.
It doesn't smell like
open butt in here.
Peter?
Huh, he's usually up by now
dry-heaving in the shower.
Hi, I'm pink-eyed Bob Costas,
live from our Pyeongchang studios,
here to bring you breaking news,
and occasionally blink off-synch
in an attempt to satisfy
my searing eye itchiness.
A U.S. tourist, Peter Griffin,
has been apprehended by North Korea
and is being held prisoner
for what I'm being told
is trespassing and doing
that thing with your eyes
that makes you look Chinese.
Damn it. Why does Peter have
to ruin every family vacation?
Just like he ruined our
trip to La La Land.
Hey, guy who's never
been uncool in a movie,
I requested "Dominick the Donkey"
like an hour ago.
It's Christmastime, and I
want greaseball songs.
♪ Hey, chingedy ching,
hee-haw, hee-haw ♪
♪ It's Dominick the donkey ♪
♪ Chingedy ching, hee-haw, hee-haw ♪
♪ The Italian Christmas donkey ♪
♪ La, la, la-la ♪
Ooh, like the movie!
♪ La-la, la, la, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la,
la-lee, oh, dah! ♪
Again.
Hey, sorry about last night, bro.
- No hard feelings?
- Yes, hard feelings.
I told you, I really liked her.
Yo, relax. We only had awesome sex.
Geez. All right, see you later.
I got to go wash Tara's
lipstick off my ass.
Well, at least I have a side,
you neutral Swiss cowards!
Oh, hey, Stewie, how's it going?
Terrible. Johnny Weir's
making my life a nightmare.
I really thought I had a
shot with Tara Lipinski,
and he ruined it.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You want me to take him out for you?
Really? You'd do that for me?
Of course. I owe you for
getting me that job
with Gloria Allred.
They say if you get a job
doing what you love,
you never work a day in your life.
Now it's clothes, now it's clothes,
now it's clothes.
This is for my brother, you
Tom Hiddleston lookalike!
- You serious, bro?
- Oh, no.
Now you're gonna beat me
up like a Batman fight,
only with gay words.
_
Kids, Brian, I've got some bad news.
Your father has been
kidnapped by North Korea.
We've got to save him.
But my race is this afternoon.
I know, but your father needs us.
I don't care. Where was
he when I needed help?
Where were any of you guys?
This was supposed to be my week.
Down here, it's my time.
It's my time down here!
- Is that from Goonies?
- I think so, yeah.
So you guys can all go.
But I'm staying here,
and I'm competing.
And I'm gonna go inside,
outside, inside, outside.
And I'm gonna get 'em on the run, boys.
And once I get 'em on the run,
I'm gonna keep 'em on the run.
Wow, she knows a lot of
Sean Astin speeches.
Go. You don't care.
The only thing you care about
is nugs, chilling and grindage.
Encino Man. Sean Astin, deep cut.
Me? Oh...
Racers, take your mark.
Go, everyone but her.
Wait, before you kill me,
can you at least give
me an extra bullet
so I can pretend to
catch one in my teeth?
Lacey Chabert!
Meg!
_
Meg, that was amazing!
But how we gonna get out of here?
- We're surrounded.
- There's only one way.
An impossible video game escape.
Ooh, can it be GoldenEye?
- Sure.
- Yes!
_
Bond. James Bond.
Don't worry, Meg, it's less
sad because they don't bleed.
Oh, don't shoot this guy.
He was nice to me.
Aw, never mind.
These guys are terrible shots.
I love this almost James Bond music.
Meg, this is what 1997 looked like.
It's my turn next try.
I want to go next.
You think one guy had to
shovel this whole walkway?
Oh, great, more stairs.
This is how you know we're done.
Peter, you're safe!
Yep, and it's all thanks to Meg.
But, Meg, what about your race?
Well, I realized that
it wasn't worth doing
if you guys weren't there with me.
Oh, Meg, we are so sorry
for how we treated you this week.
You may not have won a
gold medal in the games,
but you won one in our hearts.
What do you say, guys,
should we go home?
I don't know, I'm thinking maybe we can
hang out a little bit longer,
see what else Korea has to offer...
Uh-oh.
No! You leave Korea now!
Meet me wherever I land!
Peter landed somewhere in the DMZ,
and was recaptured by North Korea.
Fortunately, tensions caused
by this international incident
were resolved by the steady hand
of Dennis Rodman,
who let Kim Jong-un win
in a one-on-one basketball
game against him,
continuously saying, "Oop, you got me,"
in a way that was just
convincing enough
for Kim to believe.
Thank you for watching "Bob's Burgers " on
www.FOX-fan.tv